export default [
    {
        id: 1,
        question: "Characterized by skill at understanding and profiting by circumstancesLondon is __________ city I have ever lived in.",
        options: ["the more big", "the bigger", "the most big", "the biggest"],
        answer: "the biggest",
        // category: 4
    },
    {
        id: 2,
        question: "The manager wanted to know how the computer __________ stolen from the IT room.",
        options: ["is", "gets", "was", "did"],
        answer: "was",
        // category: 3
    },
    {
        id: 3,
        question: "Who did __________ at the opera?",
        options: ["see", "saw you", "you see", "you  saw"],
        answer: "you see",
        // category: 3
    },
    {
        id: 4,
        question: "She rarely leaves home without __________ her make-up on.",
        options: ["having", "doing", "putting", "to do"],
        answer: "putting",
        // category: 3
    },
    {
        id: 5,
        question: "Jessica __________ her mother's car when the accident happened.",
        options: ["drove", "was driving", "had driven", "has been driving"],
        answer: "was driving",
        // category: 2
    },
    {       
        id: 6,
        question: "If I __________ you had cancelled our meeting I wouldn't have come!",
        options: ["had known", "have known", "knew", "know"],
        answer: "had known",
        // category: 1
    },
    {
        id: 7,
        question: "My friend tells me Gary is going out with Angelina, __________ I find unbelievable.",
        options: ["who", "which", "that", "whose"],
        answer: "which",
        // category: 2
    },
    {
        id: 8,
        question: "I'm not very interested __________ Formula One.",
        options: ["about", "for", "to", "in"],
        answer: "in",
        // category: 4
    },
    {
        id: 9,
        question: "Could you __________ me this DVD for a week, please?",
        options: ["rent", "borrow", "owe", "lend"],
        answer: "lend",
        // category: 4
    },
    {
        id: 10,
        question: "Surely Mark __________ you if he has problems with your behaviour.",
        options: ["had told", "would have told", "must have told", "will tell"],
        answer: "will tell",
        // category: 4
    },
    {
        id: 11,
        question: "Able to reinforce sound by sympathetic vibrationsThe weather has been awful. We have had very __________ sunshine this week.",
        options: ["little", "a few", "a little", "few"],
        answer: "little",
        // category: 1
    },
    {
        id: 12,
        question: "I always go to the pub __________ Thursdays.",
        options: ["at", "in", "on", "by"],
        answer: "on",
        // category: 3
    }
];
